A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Fourth Administration, Subseries 37.4 FA439C
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Fourth Administration, Subseries 37.4
1971-1973
Rockefeller Archive Center
New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller)
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
FA439C
1.14 Cubic Feet 1.14 microfilm reels.
Conditions Governing Access
Microfilm user copies are open for research. The archival material has been reformatted. Access to the original paper records is restricted.
Arrangement
Series 37 is arranged into 4 subseries: Subseries 1: First Administration, 1959-1962. Subseries 2: Second Administration, 1963-1966. Subseries 3: Third Administration, 1967-1970. Subseries 4: Fourth Administration, 1971-1973. Material is arranged alphabetically by subject within each subseries.
Scope and Contents
Major subjects contained in the files include: Administration. Aging. Agriculture. Authorities and Commissions. Banking. Civil Defense. Commemorative Observance. Conservation. Consumers. Correction. Disasters. Discrimination. Education. Executive Clemency. Extradition. Fiscal. Fund raising. Government. Health & Sanitation. Honorary Designation. Horse Racing. Housing. Insurance. Investigations. Invitations. Judiciary. Labor. Law. Legislation. Licensing. Mental Hygiene. Military and Naval. Organizations. Parks and Recreation facilities. Personnel Administration. Politics. Property. Public Safety. Public Utilities. Public Works. Regrets. Resignations and Vacancies. Statements. Transportation. Veterans. Welfare. Youth.
Other Finding Aids
Other available finding aid for Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Series 37 include:
FA439 Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, First Administration, Series 37.1
FA439A Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Second Administration, Series 37.2
FA439B Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Third Administration, Series 37.3
- Fourth Administration, 1971-1973; 4; 114 microform reels
  - Administration (Reel 1, Reel 2, Reel 3, Reel 4)
    - Executive Chamber (Reel 1, Reel 2)
      - Cabinet (Reel 1, Frame 27)
      - Governor's Itinerary (Reel 1, Frame 33)
      - Equipment (Reel 1, Frame 55)
      - Inauguration (Reel 1)
        - Invitation List (Reel 1, Frame 57)
        - Seating Charts (Reel 1, Frame 106)
        - General (Reel 1, Frame 110)
      - Mail Reports
        - 1971 April 26-1974 (Reel 1, Frame 121)
        - 1970 December 28-1971 April 19 (Reel 2, Frame 17)
      - Mailing Lists (Reel 2, Frame 27)
      - Memos to Department and Agency Heads (Reel 2, Frame 34)
      - Personnel (Reel 2)
        - Appointments (Reel 2, Frame 57)
        - Commendation (Reel 2, Frame 62)
        - Resignation (Reel 2, Frame 65)
        - General (Reel 2, Frame 66)
      - Press Conference (Reel 2, Frame 84)
      - Procedures (Reel 2, Frame 108)
      - Purchases (Reel 2, Frame 109)
      - Records (Reel 2, Frame 110)
      - Women's Unit (Reel 2)
        - General (Reel 2, Frame 121)
        - Interdepartmental Committee for Volunteers (Reel 2, Frame 128)
      - General (Reel 2, Frame 130)
      - Executive Mansion (Reel 2, Frame 144)
    - Department of State (Reel 2, Frame 152)
    - General (Reel 2, Reel 3, Reel 4)
      - Agency Reports (Reel 2, Frame 171)
      - Area Council (Reel 2, Frame 175)
      - Consultants (Reel 2, Frame 185)
      - Council on Architects (Reel 2, Frame 190)
      - Executive Orders (Reel 2, Reel 3)
        - 1972-1973 (Reel 2, Frame 193)
        - 1971 (Reel 3, Frame 14)
      - Management Advisory Council (Reel 3, Frame 32)
      - Modern State in the Changing World Study (Reel 3, Frame 35)
      - Office of Planning Services (Reel 3, Frame 46)
      - Regional Planning (Reel 3, Frame 51)
      - Resolution (Reel 3, Frame 75)
      - Regional Planning (Reel 3, Frame 76)
      - Meetings (Reel 3, Reel 4)
        - Town Meetings
          - Binghamton (Reel 3, Frame 87)
          - Buffalo (Reel 3, Frame 107)
          - Corning-Elmira (Reel 3, Frame 132)
          - Lake Placid (Reel 3, Frame 155)
          - Long Island (Reel 3, Frame 168)
          - Olean (Reel 3, Frame 190)
          - Poughkeepsie (Reel 3, Frame 203)
          - Queens
            - 1972 December-1973 (Reel 3, Frame 232)
            - 1971-1972 November (Reel 4, Frame 14)
          - Rochester (Reel 4, Frame 24)
          - Syracuse (Reel 4, Frame 69)
          - Utica (Reel 4, Frame 86)
          - Utica-Rome (Reel 4, Frame 101)
          - General (Reel 4, Frame 108)
        - General (Reel 4, Frame 142)
    - General (Reel 4)
      - Miscellaneous (Reel 4, Frame 161)
  - Aging
    - Problems of (Reel 4, Reel 5)
      - Governor's Conference on Aging (Reel 4, Frame 207)
      - Housing (Reel 4, Frame 208)
      - Office of Aging (Reel 4, Frame 217)
      - Tax Exemption (Reel 4, Frame 247)
      - White House Conference (Reel 4, Reel 5)
        - 1972 March-May (Reel 4, Frame 248)
        - 1971-1972 November (Reel 5, Frame 18)
    - General (Reel 5)
      - Recreation (Reel 5, Frame 69)
      - Senior Citizens (Reel 5, Frame 71)
      - Miscellaneous (Reel 5, Frame 89)
  - Agriculture (Reel 5)
    - Department of (Reel 5)
      - Agriculture and Markets (Reel 5)
        - Animal Industry (Reel 5, Frame 109)
        - Fairs (Reel 5)
          - County (Reel 5, Frame 119)
          - State Fair (Reel 5, Frame 122)
          - General (Reel 5, Frame 127)
        - Letters of Commendation (Reel 5, Frame 129)
        - Food Control (Reel 5, Frame 129)
        - General (Reel 5, Frame 149)
    - Products (Reel 5)
      - Apples (Reel 5, Frame 159)
      - Milk (Reel 5, Frame 160)
      - General (Reel 5, Frame 170)
    - General (Reel 5)
      - Resolutions (Reel 5, Frame 183)
      - General (Reel 5, Frame 185)
  - Authorities & Commissions (Reel 5, Reel 6, Reel 7, Reel 8, Reel 9, Reel 10, Reel 11, Reel 12, Reel 13, Reel 14, Reel 15)
    - Acupuncture (Reel 5, Frame 204)
    - Adirondack (Reel 5, Reel 6)
      - 1971 April-1973 (Reel 5, Frame 206)
      - 1971 January-April (Reel 6, Frame 19)
    - Albany Port District (Reel 6, Frame 125)
    - America in Third Century (Bicentennial Commission) (Reel 6, Frame 129)
    - Appalachian Regional Commission (Reel 6, Frame 162)
    - Athletic Commission (Reel 6, Frame 189)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (Reel 6, Frame 192)
    - Atomic & Space Development Authority (Reel 6, Reel 7)
      - 1972 March-1973 October (Reel 6, Frame 194)
      - 1970 December-1973 October (Reel 7, Frame 14)
    - Attica Commission (Reel 7, Frame 34)
    - Battery Park City Authority (Reel 7, Frame 43)
    - Bingo Control Commission (Reel 7, Frame 49)
    - Commission for the Blind & Visually Handicapped (Reel 7, Frame 63)
    - Bridge Authority (Reel 7, Frame 67)
    - Buffalo Sewer Authority (Reel 7, Frame 71)
    - Catskills (Reel 7, Frame 103)
    - Central New York Regional Market Authority (Reel 7, Frame 108)
    - Central New York Transportation Authority (Reel 7, Frame 111)
    - Charter Revision Commission (Reel 7, Frame 113)
    - Civil Defense Commission (Reel 7, Frame 127)
    - Correction Commission (Reel 7, Frame 141)
    - Court System (Reel 7, Frame 143)
    - Commission on Critical Choices for America (Reel 7, Frame 148)
    - Culture Resources (Reel 7, Frame 251)
    - Delaware River Basin (Reel 8, Frame 18)
    - State Dormitory Authority (Reel 8, Frame 26)
    - Drug Laws (Reel 8, Frame 32)
    - East Hudson Parking Authority (Reel 8, Frame 89)
    - Education Commission of States (Reel 8, Frame 113)
    - Eminent Domain (Reel 8, Frame 150)
    - Erie Canal (Reel 8, Frame 155)
    - Great Lakes River Basin (Reel 8, Frame 181)
    - New York State Harness Racing Commission (Reel 8, Frame 215)
    - New York State Facilities Development Corporation
      - 1972-1973 (Reel 8, Frame 225)
      - 1971 (Reel 9, Frame 11)
    - Future of Horse Racing in New York State (Reel 9, Frame 25)
    - Hudson River Valley Commission (Reel 9, Frame 41)
    - Committee of Intergovernmental Relations (Reel 9, Frame 46)
    - Interstate Oil Compact Commission (Reel 9, Frame 57)
    - Interstate Mining Compact Commission (Reel 9, Frame 62)
    - Interstate Sanitation Commission (Reel 9, Frame 63)
    - New York State Commission on Investigation (Reel 9, Frame 86)
    - Job Development Authority (Reel 9, Frame 104)
    - Jones Beach State Parkway Authority (Reel 9, Frame 121)
    - Lake George Park Authority (Reel 9, Frame 136)
    - Legislative & Judicial Salaries Commission (Reel 9, Frame 137)
    - Liquor Authority (Reel 9, Frame 146)
    - Living Costs & the Economy (Reel 9, Frame 166)
    - Manhattan & Bronx Surface Transit (Reel 9, Frame 171)
    - Manpower Resources Commission (Reel 9, Frame 183)
    - Metropolitan Transit Authority (Reel 9, Frame 193)
    - Monroe County Water Authority (Reel 9, Frame 215)
    - Multistate Tax Compact Commission (Reel 9, Frame 219)
    - Narcotic Addiction Control Commission (Reel 9, Reel 10)
      - 1973 (Reel 9, Frame 225)
      - 1971-1972 (Reel 10, Frame 14)
    - Nassau Bridge Authority (Reel 10, Frame 28)
    - New England River Basin Commission (Reel 10, Frame 33)
    - New York City Commission to Investigate (Reel 10, Frame 39)
    - New York City Transit Authority (Reel 10, Frame 66)
    - New York State Commission to Investigate (Reel 10, Frame 87)
    - Niagara Frontier Transit Authority (Reel 10, Frame 97)
    - Off Track Betting Commission (Reel 10, Frame 106)
    - Ohio River Basin Commission (Reel 10, Frame 110)
    - Onondoga County Water Authority (Reel 10, Frame 113)
    - Parking Authority (Reel 10, Frame 118)
    - Public Employee Pension & Retirement (Reel 10, Frame 132)
    - Port Authority of New York & New Jersey (Reel 10, Reel 11, Reel 12)
      - Minutes of Meetings
        - 1973 May 10-November (Reel 10, Frame 142)
        - 1972-1973 May 10 (Reel 11, Frame 16)
      - General (Reel 11)
        - 1972 (Reel 11, Frame 162)
      - Minutes of Meetings (Reel 12)
        - 1971 (Reel 12, Frame 18)
      - General (Reel 12)
        - 1971 (Reel 12, Frame 162)
    - Power Authority (Reel 12, Frame 188)
    - Temporary Commission on Powers of Local Government (Reel 12, Frame 197)
    - Public Service Commission (Reel 12, Reel 13)
      - 1971 August-1973 (Reel 12)
      - 1971 January-July (Reel 13, Frame 17)
    - Fleichmann Commission (Reel 13, Frame 26)
    - Quarter Horse Racing Commission (Reel 13, Frame 41)
    - Rochester-Genesee Regional Transportation Authority (Reel 13, Frame 78)
    - Revise the Social Services Law (Reel 13, Frame 106)
    - Suffolk County Water Authority (Reel 13, Frame 115)
    - Susquehanna River Basin Commission (Reel 13, Frame 119)
    - Thousand Island Bridge Authority (Reel 13, Frame 127)
    - New York State Thruway Authority (Reel 13, Frame 139)
    - Triborough Bridge & Tunnel Authority (Reel 13, Frame 209)
    - Tri-State Regional Planning Commission (Reel 13, Reel 14)
      - 1973 (Reel 13, Frame 223)
      - 1971-1972 (Reel 14, Frame 16)
    - Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor (Reel 14, Frame 46)
    - National Study Commission on Water Pollution (Reel 14, Frame 68)
    - Others (Reel 14, Reel 15)
      - A-T (Reel 14, Frame 85)
      - U-Z (Reel 15, Frame 15)
    - General
      - Resolutions (Reel 15, Frame 25)
      - Miscellaneous (Reel 15, Frame 40)
  - Banking (Reel 15)
    - Department of (Reel 15, Frame 41)
    - Banks (Reel 15)
      - A-Z (Reel 15, Frame 48)
      - General (Reel 15, Frame 62)
    - General (Reel 15)
      - Mortgages (Reel 15)
      - Miscellaneous (Reel 15, Frame 69)
  - Civil Defense, Subject (Reel 15)
    - Federal (Reel 15)
      - General (Reel 15, Frame 104)
    - State (Reel 15)
      - Fallout Shelter (Reel 15, Frame 106)
      - General (Reel 15, Frame 108)
    - General (Reel 15)
      - Resolutions (Reel 15, Frame 112)
      - General (Reel 15, Frame 112)
  - Commerce (Reel 15, Reel 16, Reel 17)
    - Department of (Reel 15, Reel 16)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 15, Frame 115)
      - Business Promotions (Reel 15)
        - Conventions (Reel 15, Frame 118)
        - General (Reel 15, Frame 138)
      - Business Research (Reel 15, Frame 215)
      - Business Services (Reel 15)
        - 1973 (Reel 15, Frame 218)
      - Radio, Television & Motion Picture (Reel 15)
        - General (Reel 15, Frame 229)
      - Job Incentives (Reel 15, Frame 236)
      - Business Services (Reel 15)
        - 1971-1972 (Reel 15, Frame 239)
      - Radio, Television & Motion Picture
        - 60 Minutes
          - 1963 March-October (Reel 15, Frame 247)
          - 1973 March (Reel 16, Frame 15)
        - David Frost Show (Reel 16, Frame 18)
        - Meet the Press (Reel 16, Frame 47)
        - General (Reel 16, Frame 57)
      - Science & Technology Foundation (Reel 16, Frame 96)
      - Tourism & Travel (Reel 16, Frame 116)
      - Washington Office (Reel 16, Frame 127)
      - World Expo 74 (Reel 16, Frame 128)
      - General (Reel 16, Frame 130)
    - General (Reel 16, Reel 17)
      - Business Advisory Comm on Management Improvement (Reel 16, Frame 152)
      - Business & Financial Advisory Committee (Reel 16, Frame 168)
      - Business Publicity (Reel 16, Frame 170)
      - Business Relocation (Reel 16, Frame 203)
      - A-X Contract (Reel 16, Frame 218)
      - Buy America (Reel 16, Frame 225)
      - Council of Economic Advisors (Reel 16, Frame 237)
      - Economic Development Council (Reel 17, Frame 14)
      - Foreign Trade (Reel 17, Frame 18)
      - World Trade Center (Reel 17, Frame 34)
      - General (Reel 17, Frame 41)
  - Consumer (Reel 17)
    - Consumer Problems: General (Reel 17, Frame 149)
  - Correction (Reel 17, Reel 18, Reel 19, Reel 20)
    - Department of (Reel 17)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 17, Frame 182)
      - N.Y. State Identification & Intelligence Systems (Reel 17, Frame 183)
      - Division of Criminal Justice Service (Reel 17, Frame 196)
      - General (Reel 17, Frame 206)
    - Institutions (Reel 17, Reel 18, Reel 19)
      - Albion (Reel 17, Frame 232)
      - Attica
        - General (Reel 17)
          - 1973 (Reel 17, Frame 234)
          - 1971-1972 (Reel 17, Frame 239)
        - Special Prosecutor (Reel 18, Frame 212)
      - Auburn (Reel 18, Frame 212)
      - Beacon (Reel 18, Frame 239)
      - Clinton (Reel 18, Frame 241)
      - Dannemora (Reel 18, Frame 254)
      - Elmira (Reel 19, Frame 14)
      - Great Meadows (Reel 19, Frame 18)
      - Green Haven (Reel 19, Frame 34)
      - Matteawan (Reel 19, Frame 64)
      - Ossining (Sing-Sing) (Reel 19, Frame 73)
      - Riker's Island (Reel 19, Frame 89)
      - Wallkill (Reel 19, Frame 91)
      - Westfield (Reel 19, Frame 95)
      - Others (Reel 19, Frame 96)
      - General (Reel 19)
        - Transfers (Reel 19, Frame 128)
        - General (Reel 19, Frame 173)
    - Parole (Reel 19, Reel 20)
      - Division of (Reel 19, Frame 219)
      - Board of (Reel 19, Frame 222)
      - Parole Cases
        - 1973 September-December (Reel 19, Frame 238)
        - 1973 August (Reel 20, Frame 16)
      - General (Reel 20, Frame 58)
    - General (Reel 20)
      - Prison Reform (Reel 20, Frame 72)
      - Resolutions (Reel 20, Frame 97)
      - Select Committee on Correctional Institutions (Reel 20, Frame 102)
      - Miscellaneous (Reel 20, Frame 122)
  - Disaster (Reel 20, Reel 21)
    - Beach Erosion (Reel 20)
      - Rockaway (Reel 20, Frame 185)
      - General (Reel 20, Frame 188)
    - Floods (Reel 20, Reel 21)
      - Agnes
        - 1972 August-1973 (Reel 20, Frame 200)
        - 1971-1973 July (Reel 21, Frame 15)
      - Flood Control (Reel 21, Frame 63)
      - Lake Ontario (Reel 21, Frame 89)
      - General (Reel 21, Frame 105)
    - Others (Reel 21, Frame 148)
    - General (Reel 21, Frame 176)
  - Discrimination (Reel 21, Reel 22)
    - Human Rights, Division of (Reel 21, Frame 216)
    - Civil Rights (Reel 21, Frame 251)
    - Employment (Reel 21, Reel 22)
      - Employment in the News Media (Reel 21, Frame 253)
      - Minority Employment in the State Service (Reel 22, Frame 13)
      - Affirmative Action (Reel 22)
        - Buffalo (Reel 22, Frame 31)
        - Nassau & Suffolk Counties (Reel 22, Frame 126)
        - New York City (Reel 22, Frame 127)
        - Westchester (Reel 22, Frame 139)
        - General (Reel 22, Frame 142)
      - General (Reel 22, Frame 172)
    - Housing (Reel 22, Frame 197)
    - General (Reel 22)
      - Homosexuality (Sodomy) (Reel 22, Frame 203)
      - Interdepartmental Committee on Human Rights (Reel 22, Frame 207)
      - General (Reel 22, Frame 211)
  - Education (Reel 22, Reel 23, Reel 24, Reel 25, Reel 26, Reel 27, Reel 28, Reel 29)
    - Department of (Reel 22, Reel 23)
      - Commendation (Reel 22, Frame 227)
      - Board of Regents (Reel 22, Frame 228)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation (Reel 22, Frame 237)
      - Jack Chen (Reel 22, Frame 239)
      - General (Reel 22, Reel 23)
        - 1973 (Reel 22, Frame 251)
        - 1971-1972 (Reel 23, Frame 14)
    - Colleges (Reel 23, Reel 24, Reel 25, Reel 26)
      - Adelphi (Reel 23, Frame 23)
      - Albany (Reel 23, Frame 26)
      - Baruch (Reel 23, Frame 34)
      - Binghamton (Reel 23, Frame 44)
      - Brockport (Reel 23, Frame 46)
      - Brooklyn (Reel 23, Frame 48)
      - Brooklyn Polytechnic (Reel 23, Frame 49)
      - Broome Community College (Reel 23, Frame 61)
      - Buffalo (Reel 23, Frame 62)
      - University of Chicago (Reel 23, Frame 86)
      - City University (Reel 23, Frame 89)
      - Coblekill (Reel 23, Frame 138)
      - Columbia (Reel 23, Frame 142)
      - Cornell (Reel 23, Frame 148)
      - Cortland (Reel 24, Frame 15)
      - Dartmouth (Reel 24, Frame 18)
      - Dowling (Reel 24, Frame 24)
      - Downstate Medical Center (Reel 24, Frame 25)
      - Empire State (Reel 24, Frame 29)
      - Farmingdale (Reel 24, Frame 32)
      - Harvard (Reel 24, Frame 35)
      - Hofstra (Reel 24, Frame 37)
      - Hunter (Reel 24, Frame 39)
      - Kingsborough Community (Reel 24, Frame 48)
      - Long Island (Stonybrook) (Reel 24, Frame 51)
      - New Paltz (Reel 24, Frame 71)
      - New York University (Reel 24, Frame 74)
      - Oneonta (Reel 24, Frame 91)
      - Pace (Reel 24, Frame 94)
      - Plattsburgh (Reel 24, Frame 96)
      - Purchase (Reel 24, Frame 100)
      - Queens (Reel 24, Frame 106)
      - Rensaleer Polytechnic (Reel 24, Frame 108)
      - St. John's (Reel 24, Frame 110)
      - St. Lawrence (Reel 24, Frame 114)
      - Siena (Reel 24, Frame 115)
      - Syracuse (Reel 24, Frame 116)
      - United States Military Academy, West Point (Reel 24, Frame 153)
      - United States Naval Academy, Annapolis (Reel 24, Frame 155)
      - Upstate Medical Center (Reel 24, Frame 156)
      - Yeshiva (Reel 24, Frame 158)
      - Others (Reel 24, Reel 25)
        - A-N (Air Force Academy - Notre Dame) (Reel 24, Frame 176)
        - S-Z (St. Bonaventure - Yale) (Reel 25, Frame 16)
      - General (Reel 25)
        - Campus Disorders (Reel 25, Frame 66)
        - General (Reel 25, Frame 68)
      - Finances (Reel 25, Reel 26)
        - Federal Aid (Reel 25, Frame 104)
        - State Aid (Reel 25, Frame 128)
        - General (Reel 26, Frame 16)
      - Museums & Historical Sites (Reel 26)
        - Albany Institute of History & Art (Reel 26, Frame 29)
        - American Museum of Natural History (Reel 26, Frame 31)
        - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Reel 26, Frame 41)
        - Museum of Modern Art (Reel 26, Frame 43)
        - Philadelphia Museum of Art (Reel 26, Frame 49)
        - The Smithsonian Institute (Reel 26, Frame 50)
        - Others (A-Z) (Reel 26, Frame 53)
        - New York State Historical Trust (Reel 26, Frame 78)
        - General (Reel 26, Frame 81)
    - Schools (Reel 26)
      - Schools of the Deaf (A-Z) (Reel 26, Frame 91)
      - Others (A-Z) (Reel 26, Frame 93)
      - General (Reel 26, Frame 185)
    - State University (Reel 26, Reel 27)
      - Construction Fund (Reel 26, Frame 190)
      - Master Plan (Reel 26, Frame 198)
      - Proposed College Upper Division Utica-Rome (Reel 26, Frame 208)
      - Scholarships (Reel 26, Frame 215)
      - General (Reel 26, Reel 27)
        - 1972 August-1973 (Reel 26, Frame 224)
        - 1971-1972 July (Reel 27, Frame 14)
    - General (Reel 27)
      - Adult Education (Reel 27, Frame 43)
      - A Better Chance (ABC) (Reel 27, Frame 52)
      - Saratoga Performing Arts Center (Reel 27, Frame 54)
      - Art (Reel 27)
        - Art Centers (A-Z) (Reel 27, Frame 55)
        - Art Galleries (Reel 27, Frame 81)
        - New York City Council on Art (Reel 27, Frame 93)
        - General (Reel 27, Frame 124)
        - Miscellaneous (Reel 27, Frame 148)
      - Driver Education (Reel 27, Frame 168)
      - Educational Television (Reel 27, Frame 170)
      - Food Programs (Reel 27, Frame 177)
      - Governor's Committee on Scholastic Achievement (Reel 27, Frame 185)
    - Higher Education (Reel 27, Reel 28)
      - Higher Education Assistance Corporation (Reel 27, Frame 186)
      - Medical Education (Reel 27, Frame 195)
      - Scholar Incentive (Reel 27, Frame 220)
      - Task Force on Financing Higher Education (Reel 27, Frame 226)
      - Tuition (Reel 27, Frame 248)
      - General (Reel 28, Frame 14)
    - General (Reel 28, Reel 29)
      - Libraries (Reel 28)
        - A-Z (Reel 28, Frame 133)
        - General (Reel 28, Frame 145)
      - Local Problems (Reel 28, Frame 169)
      - Office of Education Performance Review (Reel 28, Frame 239)
      - Pledge of Allegiance (Reel 28, Frame 242)
      - Resolutions
        - 1973 May-December (Reel 28, Frame 245)
        - 1971-1973 May (Reel 29, Frame 17)
      - Umbrella Program (Reel 29, Frame 47)
      - Student Exchange (Reel 29, Frame 49)
      - Vocational Education (Reel 29, Frame 60)
      - Miscellaneous (Reel 29, Frame 72)
  - Environmental Conservation (Reel 29, Reel 30, Reel 31)
    - Department of (Reel 29, Reel 30, Reel 31)
      - Commendation (Reel 29, Frame 216)
      - Environmental Facilities Corporation (Reel 29, Frame 218)
      - Fish & Game (Reel 29, Frame 225)
      - Land & Forest (Reel 29, Frame 238)
      - Division of Motor Boats (Reel 29, Frame 251)
      - Pollution (Reel 30)
        - Air (Reel 30, Frame 14)
        - Noise (Reel 30, Frame 39)
        - Recycling (Reel 30, Frame 45)
        - Monroe County Landfill (Reel 30, Frame 49)
        - Monroe County Refuse Disposal (Reel 30, Frame 50)
        - Refuse Disposal (Reel 30, Frame 73)
        - Water Sewage (Reel 30, Frame 94)
        - Water (Reel 30, Frame 134)
        - General (Reel 30, Frame 194)
      - Water Resources
        - Passaic River Basin (Reel 30, Frame 208)
        - Tock Island (Reel 30, Frame 219)
        - General (Reel 30)
          - 1973 June-December (Reel 30, Frame 242)
          - 1971-1973 May (Reel 31, Frame 14)
      - Water Supply (Reel 31, Frame 55)
      - General (Reel 31)
        - Bond Issue (Reel 31, Frame 72)
        - Environmental Protection Agency (Reel 31, Frame 83)
        - Oceanography (Reel 31, Frame 86)
        - Resolutions (Reel 31, Frame 95)
        - General (Reel 31, Frame 107)
  - Executive Clemency (Reel 31, Reel 32)
    - Capital Punishment (Reel 31, Frame 167)
    - Anibal Cabo (Reel 31, Frame 215)
    - Jose Crespo (Reel 31, Frame 219)
    - Mark Fein (Reel 31, Frame 221)
    - Sandra Hall (Reel 31, Frame 236)
    - Calvin Johnson (Reel 31, Frame 238)
    - Murray Pincus (Reel 31, Frame 243)
    - Dr. Steven Shaff (Reel 31, Reel 32)
      - 1973 August-December (Reel 31, Frame 247)
      - 1972 April-July (Reel 32, Frame 15)
    - Jeffrey Smith (Reel 32, Frame 28)
    - Eugene Sugarman (Reel 32, Frame 62)